Class of 1914 Records, 1910-1985
Smith College Archives
Class of 1914 Records
1910-1985
Smith College. Class of 1914.
RG 80 UUID:eae04850-3dea-4f60-a5f2-7b9e55094773
35 boxes (23.9 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection is in 35 boxes and contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1914.
Historical Note
The Class of 1914 was the thirty-fifth entering class and the thirty-fifth graduating class of Smith College.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Class of 1914 records, 1910-1985, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1914, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, questionnaires, and other memorabilia. The Class Secretary's Notes contain biographical material as well as a necrology.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1914 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Baccalaureate Service 1914 (Box 1845, Folder 1)
- Commencement 1914 (Box 1845, Folder 2)
- Commencement Music 1914 (Box 1845, Folder 3)
- Commencement Photographs 1914 (Box 1845, Folder 4)
- Freshman Frolic 1910 (Box 1845, Folder 5)
- Freshman Grind 1910 (Box 1845, Folder 6)
- Freshman Handbook 1910 (Box 1845, Folder 7)
- Groups 1910-1914 (Box 1845, Folder 8)
- Hoop Rolling 1914 (Box 1845, Folder 9)
- Junior Frolic 1913 (Box 1845, Folder 10)
- Junior Prom 1913 (Box 1845, Folder 11)
- Junior Prom-Garden Party 1913 (Box 1845, Folder 12)
- Junior Ushers 1913 (Box 1845, Folder 13)
- Ivy Day 1914 (Box 1845, Folder 14)
- Ivy Day Photographs 1914 (Box 1845, Folder 15)
- Class Letters 1927-1957 (Box 1845, Folder 16)
- Class Letters 1958-1985 (Box 1845, Folder 17)
- Class Officers 1910-1974 (Box 1845, Folder 18)
- Necrology n.d. (Box 1845, Folder 19)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology (Box 1846, Folder 1)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology (Box 1846, Folder 2)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology 1969 (Box 1846, Folder 3)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-A (Box 1846, Folder 4)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-B (Box 1846, Folder 5)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-C (Box 1846, Folder 6)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-D (Box 1846, Folder 7)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-E (Box 1846, Folder 8)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-F (Box 1846, Folder 9)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-G (Box 1846, Folder 10)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-H (Box 1846, Folder 11)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-I-J (Box 1846, Folder 12)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-K (Box 1846, Folder 13)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-L (Box 1846, Folder 14)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-M (Box 1846, Folder 15)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-N (Box 1846, Folder 16)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-O (Box 1846, Folder 17)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-P (Box 1846, Folder 18)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-Q (Box 1846, Folder 19)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-R (Box 1846, Folder 20)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-S (Box 1846, Folder 21)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-T (Box 1846, Folder 22)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-U-V (Box 1846, Folder 23)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-W (Box 1846, Folder 24)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-X-Z (Box 1846, Folder 25)
- Class Secretary's Records (Box 1847, Folder 1)
- Class Secretary's Notes-A (Box 1847, Folder 2)
- Class Secretary's Notes-B (Box 1847, Folder 3)
- Class Secretary's Notes-C (Box 1847, Folder 4)
- Class Secretary's Notes-D (Box 1847, Folder 5)
- Class Secretary's Notes-E (Box 1847, Folder 6)
- Class Secretary's Notes-F (Box 1847, Folder 7)
- Class Secretary's Notes-G (Box 1847, Folder 8)
- Class Secretary's Notes-H (Box 1847, Folder 9)
- Class Secretary's Notes-I-J (Box 1847, Folder 10)
- Class Secretary's Notes-K (Box 1847, Folder 11)
- Class Secretary's Notes-L (Box 1847, Folder 12)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Mc-M (Box 1847, Folder 13)
- Class Secretary's Notes-N (Box 1847, Folder 14)
- Class Secretary's Notes-O (Box 1847, Folder 15)
- Class Secretary's Notes-P (Box 1847, Folder 16)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Q (Box 1847, Folder 17)
- Class Secretary's Notes-R (Box 1847, Folder 18)
- Class Secretary's Notes-S (Box 1847, Folder 19)
- Class Secretary's Notes-T (Box 1847, Folder 20)
- Class Secretary's Notes-U-V (Box 1847, Folder 21)
- Class Secretary's Notes-W (Box 1847, Folder 22)
- Class Secretary's Notes-X-Z (Box 1847, Folder 23)
- Photograph Albums n.d. (Box 1848, Folder 1)
- Photograph Albums n.d. (Box 1848, Folder 2)
- Senior Dramatics 1914 (Box 1848, Folder 3)
- Senior Dramatics-Correspondence 1914 (Box 1848, Folder 4)
- Senior Dramatics-Photographs 1914 (Box 1848, Folder 5)
- Senior Dramatics-Photographs 1914 (Box 1848, Folder 6)
- Songs n.d. (Box 1848, Folder 7)
- Sophomore Reception to 1915 1911 (Box 1848, Folder 8)
- Step Sings 1914 (Box 1848, Folder 9)
- Class Supper 1914 (Box 1848, Folder 10)
- Treasurer's File 1979-1983 (Box 1848, Folder 11)
- Vespers Service 1914 (Box 1848, Folder 12)
- Reunion Material-General (Box 1849, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1915 (Box 1849, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1917 (Box 1849, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1919 (Box 1849, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1924 (Box 1849, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1929 (Box 1849, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1934 (Box 1849, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1939 (Box 1849, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1949 (Box 1849, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1954 (Box 1849, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1959 (Box 1849, Folder 11)
  (see also Box 1850)
- Reunions 1964 (Box 1849, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1968 (Box 1849, Folder 13)
- Reunions 1969 (Box 1849, Folder 14)
- Reunions 1974 (Box 1849, Folder 15)
- Reunions 1979 (Box 1849, Folder 16)
- Reunions 1959 (Box 1850, Folder 1)
- Reunion Questionnaire 1959 (Box 1850, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1959 (Box 1850, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1959 (Box 1850, Folder 4)